

Vladimir Zaigrajew

Born on March 5th, 1998 Torun – Poland Currently living in Wroclaw

 $\Box +48\ 516\ 736\ 901$

☑ vladimir.zaigrajew@gmail.com

in vladimirzaigrajew

♥ WolodjaZ

☐ Github Blog

Language Skills

- o Polish native
- o Russian near native
- o English C1 level

Professional Skills

- o Languages Python (Mainly), C++, Java, SQL
- o CI/CD Github Actions
- Frameworks Django, Redis,

Postgres, MySQL, GIT, Docker

- AI and ML frameworks Pytorch,
 JAX/Flax, OpenCV, scikit-learn,
 Pandas, Numpy, Matplotlib, Seaborn,
 Plotly, Dash, Grafana, , W&B
- Big Data frameworks Hadoop,
 PySpark, Kubernetes (Lens), HPC (SLURM)

Research Interests

- AI and Deep learning methods
- Computer vision
- Generative models

Communication Skills

- o Time-management
- \circ Decision-making
- Teamwork and multitasking
- Team leadership and management.

About me

My fortes include the ability and passion to learn and challenge myself to improve throughout my skill set. I started my computer science career in both academia and job as a backend developer consequently progressing to Machine Learning, which has become my work and research focus. Namely, I specialize in the computer vision domain, but I am also open to other frameworks.

I am experienced in teamwork, including managing cutting-edge projects in commercial object detection and tracking. I devote significant personal time to furthering my research and widening my purview. I am a communicative, sporty, tolerant and cooperative person.

Education

2021 – 2022. Master of Science in Artificial Intelligence, Wroclaw University of Science and Technology (WUST), Poland

Thesis Title: Contrastive learning for multi-label classification (accepted for NeurIPS 2022 Workshop).

As a participant of AI Tech (government AI, ML and cybersecurity education project) I took part in WACV 2022 and ICLR 2022 international conferences.

2017 – 2021. Bachelor of Science, Wroclaw University of Science and Technology (WUST), Poland

Major: Computer Science

Minor: Applied Computer Engineering in Medicine

Thesis Title: Human activity recognition on the basis of changes of WiFi

characteristics.

Work Experience

2019 - 2022. Computer Vision Researcher and Engineer

cognitivX S.A.

- Researching optimal solutions for object detection and object tracking applying DeepStream SDK on an embedded device (NVIDIA Jetson Nano);
- Complying and managing the corporate dataset for object detection and leading the annotating group;
- Training object detection architecture and optimizing it for NVIDIA TensorRT;
- Preparing scripts in Deepstream SDK for production use with object tracking model;
- Hypertuning and optimizing object tracking and object detection models;
- \circ Preparing framework in Python for object tracking using Microsoft Azure:
- o Creating the structures for MySQL on Azure and preprocessing scripts;
- o Implementing visualizations in Dash and metrics tracking in Grafana.

Extracurricular activites

Oct 2022. Reviewed several papers for NeurIPS 2022 Workshop.

June 2022. Completed 8th PKO Night Wroclaw Half Marathon.

2014 – 2017. Represented school in inter-school soccer competition also captaining team during last year.

2006 – 2013. Played soccer in Pomorzanin Torun team.